<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tour Ghana</string>

    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    //Regions Name
    <string name="region_1">Northern Region</string>
    <string name="region_2">Eastern Region</string>
    <string name="region_3">Western Region</string>
    <string name="region_4">Ashanti Region</string>
    <string name="region_5">Brong Ahafo Region</string>


    //Northern Region Places Name
    <string name="region_place_1">Mole National Park</string>
    <string name="region_place_2">Laribanga Mosque</string>
    <string name="region_place_3">Mognori Eco-Villager</string>
    <string name="region_place_4">Zayaa Mud Mosque at Wulugu</string>
    <string name="region_place_5">Tamale Central Market</string>
    <string name="region_place_6">Nalerigu Slave Defence Wall</string>

    //Northern Region Place Details
    <string name="place_1_detail">Mole National Park is one of the cheapest safaris in Africa. A drive in the park will show you the wealth of animals that the park has. The park boasts of having nothing less than 94 different mammals, some of which are the elephants, antelopes, baboons, buffaloes, warthogs and many more. The sky of Mole National Park is also filled with the shapes of beautiful birds. As a matter of fact, there are more than 300 different bird species in the park alone.</string>
    <string name="place_2_detail">Built in the 13th century, Laribanga Mosque is the first mosque to be built in all of West Africa. The mosque still stands till today. It is considered as a holy place for the Muslims in the area.</string>
    <string name="place_3_detail">Not far from Mole National Park is the Mognori Eco-village, a village popular for its vibrant culture and tradition. You can go on interesting canoe safaris in this village where you will get to see animals like crocodiles, monkeys and birds. You can also tour round the village where you\'ll learn about the history and traditional medicines of the people. You will also be entertained with dances, some and drumming in this village.</string>
    <string name="place_4_detail">Needless to say, this mosque was built with mud but the fascinating thing about it is that it has its own unique kind of storey designs that made it a strategic location for military purposes.</string>
    <string name="place_5_detail">Tamale is the fourth largest city in Ghana and is by far the fastest growing. It has a population of 400,000 people with the majority of them being Muslims. Much of the buying and selling that goes on in the city is done in the central market which makes the market a popular one in the city and Ghana as a whole.</string>
    <string name="place_6_detail">This wall was built in the 16th century to keep out the slave traders from capturing the people of this community and trading them as slaves to the European countries. Although most of the wall is now in ruins, it is still recognizable for what it was.</string>

    //Eastern Region Places Name
    <string name="region2_place_1">Aburi Botanical Gardens</string>
    <string name="region2_place_2">Shai Hills Resource Reserve</string>
    <string name="region2_place_3">Boti Falls</string>
    <string name="region2_place_4">Umbrella Rock</string>
    <string name="region2_place_5">Tetteh Quarshie Cocoa Farm</string>
    <string name="region2_place_6">Akosombo Dam</string>
    <string name="region2_place_7">Bunso EcoPark</string>

    //Eastern Region Places Details
    <string name="region2_place1_detail">The garden is located at Aburi in the Akwapim South District of the Eastern Region and it is 30 Km North of Accra on the Akuapemhills at 1200 feet elevation. The garden can be used as a place of convalescing and has both flora and fauna. In colonial times, it was used as a retreat for official visitors and others who needed to escape the hustle and bustle of the big city. The town has comfortable weather conditions similar to that of the fall in the northeastern part of the United States, the coast of France, or Germany during the summertime. It has a comfortable spot near the coast. The botanic garden attracts people from all over Ghana, as well as many foreign visitors. At the entrance of the garden is beautiful Royal Palm trees which are one of the most popular spots in most pictures of visitors. The attraction has a large variety of traditional, medicinal plants as well as a silk-cotton tree (Ceiba pentrandra), the sole survivor of the original forest that once covered the Aburi hills. The venue is also ideal for picnics, wedding receptions amongst other events.</string>
    <string name="region2_place2_detail">The Shai Hills Resource Reserve is estimated an hour drive from Accra. Located towards the north of Accra and around the Akosombo road, the reserve is home to some of Ghana’s best wildlife. The best time to have the most sighting of the various animals like the antelopes, monkeys, bushbucks just to mention a few is in the mornings. To add to the fun there is also the opportunity to visit the Obonu tem and Se yo caves on the Hioweyo and Sayu Hills while there. If you looking for the best camping experience in the Eastern region, then Shai hills reserve is the best among all the tourist sites. Hence you have an entire package of an experience when you visit the Shai Hills Resource Reserve. Most people also choose to spend the night by booking their luxury tent or choose to camp to have a full feel of the place. One other piece of advice is to visit the place when you have your own vehicle.</string>
    <string name="region2_place3_detail">Boti falls is one of the most popular waterfalls in Ghana. It is a twin waterfall located at Boti in the Eastern Region of Ghana. These twin falls are referred to as female and male. People visit this site to swim and enjoy the feel of nature as well. At the site of the Boti Falls in Yilo Krobo District, that is where the Umbrella Rock is found. Arguably it is the most popular among all tourist sites in Eastern region.</string>
    <string name="region2_place4_detail">The Rock is roughly a 40-minute walk or hike in the forest from the falls. You can also get there by car in about 10 minutes. The Umbrella Rock which is also referred to as Akatamann, meaning ‘umbrella’ in the Akan language, is certainly a sight worth seeing. Its size can shelter up to about 12 to 15 people at once. Even though the pivot on which the top rock lies might seem small, it’s very strong and has not been able to pull or pushed down with manpower. Yearly, many tourists make it to the Boti Falls to have a feel of nature, without leaving the umbrella rock from sight. Nearby is also a rock known as the Fertility rock which is believed to bless young ladies who sit on it with twins or triplets.</string>
    <string name="region2_place5_detail">Located in mampong Akwapim, is the first cocoa farm established in the Country from seeds first brought from Fernando Po Island by the Legendary Tetteh Quarshie. From this small beginning grew a major cocoa industry. It is believed that a few of the original first trees planted by Tetteh Quarshie can still be found on the farm. Other cocoa farms were later established which has given birth to a vibrant cocoa industry in the country. It is believed that a few of the original first trees planted by Tetteh Quarshie can still be found on the farm. Relics and important artifacts used by Tetteh Quarshie are also on display at a museum which is situated on the farm.</string>
    <string name="region2_place6_detail">Akosombo Dam also known as the Akosombo Hydroelectric Project is a hydroelectric dam on the Volta River. The Dam over the years has been a major destination for educational tourism and the main source of hydroelectric power for the country. The site is located in the Akosombo gorge and it is part of the Volta River.Lake Volta is the largest man-made lake in the world. It covers 8,502 square kilometers (3,283 sq. mi) which are 3.6\% of Ghana’s land area. The dam is 132 meters high from its foundation and 660 meters long. It has created a reservoir of water of about 780-kilometer square surface area with a total storage capacity of 148 meters.</string>
    <string name="region2_place7_detail">Bunso Arboretum is a botanical garden located at Bunso in the East Akim District of the Eastern Region in Ghana.  This district is an eco-tourism site two hours drive and has about 600 tree species used for medicinal purposes. Upon visiting this forest reserve you can choose the adventure of walking on the canopy walkway, zip-lining, or horse riding activities. Children are not also left out of the fun. A playground and a canopy walk it designed just for them to have a feel of the adventure too.</string>

    //Western Region Places Name
    <string name="region3_place_1">Fort Metal Cross</string>
    <string name="region3_place_2">Akatekyi Crocodile Pond</string>
    <string name="region3_place_3">Busua Beach</string>
    <string name="region3_place_4">Nzulezu</string>
    <string name="region3_place_5">Bia National Park</string>
    <string name="region3_place_6">Cape Three Points</string>

    //Western Region Places Details
    <string name="region3_place1_detail">This castle was built 300 years ago by the British as a warehouse for gold dust, timber, and then later slaves. This tourist attraction sits on a rocky promontory which overlooks the fishing port of Dixcove. Located in a fishing village called Infuma, the area is surrounded by water suitable for canoes and small boats. Also, large ships are able to dock roughly 2 kilometers from the coast. To get to this part of the Western region from Accra, it takes approximately 4 hours by road and 45 mins by air. This is one trip promised to be filled with excitement and learning as the site holds so much of Ghana and Africa’s history and the rich culture and tradition of the people in its surroundings.</string>
    <string name="region3_place2_detail">If you love animals, specifically crocodiles, then Akatekyi Crocodile Pond in the Western region is worth the trip. The usual norm for visitors who want to see the fascinating sight of these reptiles is for the fetish priest also known as a traditional spiritual leader, to entice the crocodiles from the water with a live foul. For this reason, visitors are also encouraged to bring schnapps for libation. The crocodiles are perceived to be sacred and likewise an important part of the community of people in that area. The pond is approximately 30km west of Takoradi, the capital of the Western Region. Hence if you cannot make it all the way to Paga crocodile park in the Northern region, then you can have a similar experience just four hours from Accra.</string>
    <string name="region3_place3_detail">The Busua Beach stretch is a lovely, relaxing paradise for tourists. There are several beach resorts along the coast for visitors to lodge or spend a lovely and relaxing time with friends and family. For example, one of these popular places is the Busua Beach Resort. You can engage in lots of water sports, horse riding, or enjoy a tasty seafood meal by the ocean.</string>
    <string name="region3_place4_detail">If you are considering taking a holiday to see beautiful architecture on water, you may consider Bora Bora or the Maldives but Nzulezu in the Western region of Ghana gives you the similar experience infused with a beautiful African vibe. The main tourist attraction in the region is a village which is built at the center of Lake Tadane almost 90km west of Takoradi. The architecture is remarkable as homes are built on stilts which creates an interesting communal lifestyle to suit the water condition. Visitors are able to experience a lovely promenade through the reeds at the edge of the lake, including a trip in a dugout canoe to the village. This breathtaking site welcomes visitors on all days except Thursday which is known to be a sacred day. Thus, if you love water and adventurous travel, Nzulezu is the place to go.</string>
    <string name="region3_place5_detail">This national park in the Western region of Ghana is also a biosphere reserve home to 563 square kilometers of resource reserve. It has some of the tallest trees in West Africa and 62 different species of mammals. There are also 10 primate species, i.e chimpanzees, three species of colobus, and Pan troglodytes among many others. Bia is also the only known home to a recently discovered specie of lizard known as Agama Sylvanus. Moreover, there are also over 160 species of birds in the reserve. Hence a trip to this tourist attraction would be one of a lifetime.</string>
    <string name="region3_place6_detail">Located at the Southernmost tip of Ghana, Cape Three points is one of the most beautiful beaches along Ghana’s coast. To have a clear view of this captivating sight, you’ll need to visit the 95 year-old light house at the Cape. Cape Three Points also has a village with a number of landmarks for sightseeing which give you the opportunity to explore a cultural present and a colonial past of Ghana. There are several activities to engage in around the area like hiking, surfing and simply relaxing by the beach. A drive to Cape Three Points usually gives visitors a chance to see how rubber is harvested and if lucky a sight of some monkeys and other wildlife too. This is one trip you do not want to miss out on while in Ghana.</string>


    //Ashanti Region Places Name
    <string name="region4_place_1">Manhyia Palace</string>
    <string name="region4_place_2">Bonwire Kente Weaving Village</string>
    <string name="region4_place_3">Kejetia Market</string>
    <string name="region4_place_4">Ntonso Adinkra Village</string>
    <string name="region4_place_5">Lake Bosumtwi</string>
    <string name="region4_place_6">Bobiri Butterfly Sanctuary</string>

    //Ashanti Region Places Details
    <string name="region4_place1_detail">This palace was the seat of power of the highest chief of the Asante kingdom, Asantehene. It is located in Kumasi, the capital of the Ashanti Region. The palace was first built by the Ashantis themselves and it was so beautiful and grand that the British were impressed by the size of it when they first saw it. The palace contained many rows of books written in different languages. However, that didn\'t stop the British from leveling it during the war of the golden stool. It was later rebuilt in 1925 by the British themselves.</string>
    <string name="region4_place2_detail">It is no news that Africans put a whole lot of their resources on fashion and Ghana is no exception. Kente, for instance, is a fabric made and worn by Ghanaians for special occasions and events. The history of weaving in Africa can be traced way back to 3000BC and it has since developed, improved and evolved to what we have today. Kente fabric originated in the Asante kingdom around the 17th century and is now a fabric that is worn in all parts of Ghana and beyond today. According to history, Ota Karaban and his friend Kwaku learned everything they knew about weaving from a spider. They told a chief in Bonwire about their expenditure who later told the head chief of Asante kingdom, the Asantehene. This Asantehene later Incorporated this fabric into their culture and is still worn at important occasions till date. That fabric is the Kente fabric.</string>
    <string name="region4_place3_detail">This is by far one of the biggest markets in all of Africa. It is said to contain at least 11,000 stalls while nothing less than 40,000 people work there. It is characterized by many brown roofs that can already be seen from afar. There you will find different wares and goods for sale.</string>
    <string name="region4_place4_detail">Ntonso is where Adinkra cloth printing is done. The prints are made with dyes and stamps made from calabashes. You will be told about the history of the people, their crafts and shown how to make the prints at the Ntonso Visitor Center.</string>
    <string name="region4_place5_detail">An ancient meteorite landed in the Ashanti Region and the lake was born. He lake was said to be discovered by a hunter who chased an antelope into the lake. It is believed that the lake received the antelope like it was trying to save it from the hunter. That is why the lake is called the Antelope God Lake till today. This history makes the lake a very sacred lake to the Ashants. About 70,000 people live in the villages that surround the lake.</string>
    <string name="region4_place6_detail">The place is as beautiful as the butterflies that have found home in the place. Apart from the butterfly sanctuary, the site consists of an arboretum and forest hiking trails. The butterfly sanctuary is a home to hundreds of different butterfly species that mostly come out during the day in their colorful vibrance. In the rainforest, you will also find many scarce tree species which create a cool environment for people to relax in.</string>

    //Brong Ahafo Region Places Name
    <string name="region5_place_1">Kintampo Waterfalls</string>
    <string name="region5_place_2">Buabeng Fiema Monkey Sanctuary</string>
    <string name="region5_place_3">Buoyem Sacred Grove</string>
    <string name="region5_place_4">Tano Boase</string>


    //Brong Ahafo Region Places Details
    <string name="region5_place1_detail">The waterfall is one of the highest in Ghana, having three main drop points. The waterfall is found on the Pumpum river, one of the smaller rivers that flow from the Black Volta. The waterfall attracts its own healthy number of tourists annually and is still one of the most beautiful waterfalls in Ghana.</string>
    <string name="region5_place2_detail">Here is another place where monkeys are held with utmost respect in Africa. The monkeys are never killed or harmed because they are said to have some traditional significance to the community. In fact, the community plants fruit trees just for these monkeys. They even go an extra mile in caring for their dead monkeys. They perform funeral rites for these dead monkeys before finally laying them to rest in the cemetery that was specifically built for the sole purpose of keeping dead monkeys. The monkeys you\'ll find here are the Mona monkeys and the black silky colobus.</string>
    <string name="region5_place3_detail">This site is surrounded by hills on three different sides. The grove is home to many rock caves and different rock formations. Tourists can have fun exploring the caves, hiking the rocks and seeing far and wide from the high vantage point of the rocks. The site has a particular rock that looks like the shape of Africa and another that looks exactly like an umbrella. Interesting history is tagged with this place as the caves are considered sacred by the people and it was strategically used in the war against the Ashanti.</string>
    <string name="region5_place4_detail">This grove is also a place to visit as its many beautiful rock formations all look fascinating. The grove is said to be sacred to the people of Tanoboase because the Tano River within the grove is believed to be the dwelling place of Taakora, the greatest of the gods of the Akan people.</string>
</resources>
